

Contact Information

19 Avenue Charles de Gaulle, 38380 Saint-laurent-du-pont 0626991976 gaspard.thirion@gmail.com Holder of a Category B driving license

Main technologies

Unity 3D C#
Godot C++
Android kotlin

Languages

Français Natif

Anglais Professionnel

Extracurricular Activities

Passionate about all kind of bicycles National-level competitor in Biketrial

Gaspard Thirion

Freelance video game developer

Profile

Lifelong Unity developer, I made it my profession after graduating from Epitech. During this course, I went to study video game creation for a year in South Korea.

Numerous GameJam experiences have allowed me to become versatile, efficient in my developments, and quick to adapt to a new team.

I primarily develop tools for users (developers, artists, etc.) and gameplay/UI systems, and I have completed projects in AR and VR.

Experiences

Syslor - Unity3D developer

Development of mobile applications and internal tools in the Unity3D engine. Creation of advanced 3D and 2D visualizations, including some AR.

Conversion of a Unity3D solution to native Android (Kotlin). Permanent position: January 2021 - June 2022 (1 year 6 months) Freelance: Since June 2022 (2 years) on various projects

Freelance developer

Proxima City (2020): Eco-friendly city builder on Android with an AR component.

Barrier Squad (2021): Integration of Google Play Games and Unity Ads for an Android tower defense game.

Aviator (2023): Branching narrative game of about twenty minutes. Uses an Android tablet for game control an Premier Servi (in progress): Hide-and-seek party game intended for release on Steam and Switch.

Human Games - Unity3D internship

Development of games for professional training in a VR environment. September 2019 - February 2020 (6 months)

ITC Tatto - C++ internship

Development of C++ programs using the QT library to facilitate stock management and the online listing of new products.

April 2018 - July 2018 (6 months)

Formation

EPITECH: 2015 - 2020

Title of IT Expert

Keimyung University: 2018 - 2019

Exchange student, Computer Games and Programming curriculum

La Malgrange: 2012 - 2015

High School Diploma in Science (SVT) with Mathematics specialization